ED
Hello everyone!
Hello!
Yes! So, today I will be answering 100 questions!
Let's go!
Yes! Yes! My name is Karin Tachibana from Miyagi Prefecture!
My image color is pink!
And I am the leader of Iginari Talk!
I'm looking forward to working with you!
My nickname is "Karen-kun".
My birthday is October 21, 2003.
What are you doing on the day the world ends?
On the day the world ends, I would like to say, uh, Mr. Tohoku.
What kind of yakitori would you order?
I especially like liver and sand eel.
Do you prefer yakitori with sauce or salt? Or salt?
Salt!
Do you pick white streaks of mandarin oranges?
I heard that you take the white streaks out of mandarin oranges.
Well, I was into it for a while, but I prefer the ones without the white streaks.
What is your favorite hairstyle?
Half twin!
Do you like spicy food?
I've never had it before, so I want to try it. Super spicy.
What color do you dye your hair?
Pink! Um, whitish pink.
Do you believe in psychics? Well, I'm sure there are.
Personal accompaniments? For rice, um, seaweed tsukudani.
What about the noodles? I like one side.
Kaetama? I don't eat much ramen, but I think I could eat 2, 2, 3.
My must-have for expeditions is a pair of fluffy pajamas.
If you were in a band, which band would you be in?
Electron! I've done it once.
I might be able to do it.
Would you peel and eat snow? Yes, I do.
Depends on the day? I don't know. I peel it and eat it.
What is the latest dream you had? What is the latest dream you had?What dreams have you had recently? What was the dream you had recently?
I don't know, I dreamed of running around in a garden. What is your favorite season?
I guess autumn. Because of pumpkins. Rice or bread? Bread?
Bread. Even if I like rice-flour bread. Idol?
What flavor of ramen do you prefer? Pork bone? Opechan? I like
Door to anywhere or free transportation. Anywhere door!
What do you like? Negitoro and corn gunkan. If you could figure it out, what would it be? I don't know.
Is it your position? What's that?
He said if he could figure out the name of the group...
Well, I like Inari and Okusan.
I wonder...
Inari and his friends
and their merry band of friends
Mmmmmmmm...
What is your favorite word?
You only live once
And youth.
Where would you like to travel in Japan?
Hmmm...
Akita, Gunma
Gunma, to see my grandpa.
Where would you like to go on an overseas trip?
Well, I have a lot of places.
Um, Korea, the U.S., France, Paraguay? I'd like to go somewhere.
What do you do on your days off?
Well, I'm just kind of wandering around, going somewhere for fun.
Or live on my own.
Mmm-hmm.
How many meals a day?
Three meals a day with Mr. Tohoku?
I don't know.
If I'm not with Mr. Northeast, I eat about 2 meals a day.
What is your favorite animal?
Cats.
Ignatius, or something like that.
Favorite singer and song?Who is your favorite singer and what is your favorite song?
Favorite singer and favorite song?
Uh, singer.
By singer, you mean a singer?
Yushka.
Mmm...
Pure Clear Boy
But lately I've been listening to Macaroni & Pizzazz.
What's your favorite English word?
Let's see...
I don't know.
Blue.
Do you have a driver's license?
I don't have one. But I'd like to get one.
How fast are you at 50 meters?
Like 12 seconds?
I don't know. I don't know where I was.
What is your favorite subject?
Home economics. I love home economics textbooks. I read them all the time.
Are you shy?
What's your boom?
Buying lots of food samples. I am happy.
If you were to compare yourself with one kanji character, what would it be?
Strange.
Can you show it?
Yes, I can. Make a high voice and a low voice.
Next show
What do you think about during a live performance?
I often lose my memory during a live performance.
I'm just having fun.
I live my life with the feeling of wanting to convey and share this feeling.
Which song is the most fun to sing live?
I think the song that gets the best intro is "Mr. President".
What's your favorite nabe ingredient?
Nabe ingredients?
Tofu?
What is your favorite oden ingredient?What is your favorite oden ingredient?
Grilled tofu?
Who do you admire?
Yes, I do.
If you could take one thing with you to a deserted island, what would it be?
Because...
I don't know.
A notebook? A notebook and a pen.
Paper.
Pen.
If you could go to the notebook, who would you bring? I don't know.
Who would survive?
Hmmm, Run-chan?
Run-chan is rather stubborn.
I think she'll survive.
Who would you switch with?
I'd like to go see the cat in the house.
If you were a man, which member would you like to date?
Um... Yuna.
She's so cute and seems to have fun wherever she goes.
What sport would you like to play?
Well, I've always wanted to try Piar's Kabaddi.
The best dancer in the world OR...oh, wow!
I want to be the best singer in the world.
I'll be the best dancer in the world. I can't sing. I've found the one and only.
How do I get to be the tallest person I want to be? I'll never get fat.
I'll never get fat.
A word to the uninitiated.
I think it doesn't matter how long we've known each other, it's the depth of our love that counts, so let's be together for a long time to come.
What song would you recommend to a chick?
I think feeling will save him. Very nice lyrics.
What time do you go to bed and wake up? About...
I go to bed around 1:00 and wake up around...
9:00? I don't know.
Do you wear clothes to bed? Pajamas? I love pajamas. They're so cute.
So, if you lived in the world, would you live in the country? The city?
I'd live in the country, go to the city.This is the ultimate... a place to live in the country, a place to play in the city.
What color would you change from one member to another?
I don't think I'd want to give up pink.
The most expensive pair of earphones I ever bought.
I've lost them four or five times. I've lost headphones.
What's your biggest fear?
I was surprised the other day when I met Sadness for the first time.
What's your favorite onigiri?
Shake?
What would you like to do in the entertainment industry?
Voice acting, theater, musicals.
Do you seed the watermelon first?
What's the part on the surface where you pick them out first?
Yeah, yeah, that's the first time I've ever been asked that.
Is there anything you believed in when you were little that you can't think about now?
I don't know.
Well, I used to suck the nectar out of flowers because it tasted so good.
How many questions are you on? Wow, I think I'm on, like, 58 or something.
Wow, that's not even close. I'm so disappointed!
Oh no. What were you like when you were little?
Well, she was very innocent. She was very young.
Water or tea? Tea?
Or tea?
If you could produce any of your own songs, what would they be?
Something like "Youth.
Something heavy, like a heavy cone.
What kind of karaoke box do you use?
Ainyoung's "Tonight's the Night".
What do you do at the moment of New Year's Eve?
Mr. Distant... everyone is flying.
He's flying too.
Squeeze time, please!
Yes, ma'am.
What do you do on the move?
When I'm on the road, I'm either sleeping or making friends with my phone.
What do you always order when you watch a movie?
A big size drink.Big size drink
I was in the art club and vice-president.
What is your difficult song?
I don't know, what is a difficult song.
Lately, I think Musubi is difficult.
Hamon is also difficult.
The reason I got into show business was because I went to see Momoguro-san's live performance,
Onagawa scouted me there.
Do you believe in fate? I do! If I don't believe, I can't start!
I believe in everything!
Who is your favorite YouTuber?
There is a YouTuber who makes food samples.
He has a YouTube channel, and I watch it a lot.
What were you into when you were little?
I don't know.
Drawing pictures on banana faces with toothpicks.
What is your favorite thing about yourself?
My Buddha-like smile!
My hobbies are making food samples and looking at them.
Do you confess your feelings to someone? Or do you wait? I'm definitely a wait-and-see kind of girl.
Are you good at parent-child relationships? I'm not good at it. I once drowned in shallow water.
Where would you like to go with the Iginari Corps? I'd like to go see my grandpa.
Japanese food? Western food? Japanese food? Japanese food? Japanese food
If you could only eat the same food for the rest of your life, what would it be?
My uncle.
Where would you like to perform live? Budokan.
If you were an animal, how would you describe yourself? I am often called a cat. I used to be a dog.
If you were to compare each member to an animal, how would you describe yourself? Lun-chan is a whitish cat.
Rinne is that expensive cat, and Yuna is...
Yuna is a monkey?
Yuna is a waka, and Waka is lazy.
Waka is lazy. Waka is... She's cute, but not the laziest.
Waka, Pearl, Pearl...
What's a pearl? Pearls
Pearls?
Pearls?Pearl?
Pearls.
Because they're green.
Frogs.
And Karen is a cat.
And Mon-chan is...
Mon-chan is a dog
Myu is...
Myuu, what kind of animal is that?
Is Myu a Myu?
Ka-ya, ka-ya, ka-ya..,
A dog, a dog, a medium-sized dog.
Yes, sir.
In a word, what is your selling point?
Love and passion
Which singer would you like to have an interview with?
Singer you would like to interview?
Singers?
What would it be?
We are looking for singers we would like to have an interview with.
What part-time jobs have you had?
I've worked at a food store, a deli, and a food service center.
I'd also like to work at a convenience store and in a kitchen.
Yes, there are many!
What is your favorite snack?
My favorite snack... macaroon ice cream.
What is your favorite part?
Well...
The way you love Toukku.
You are always supportive and kind.
The way you always wrap me up in your love.
And the way you always smile at me.
I love you!
What do you want everyone to fix?
What do you want me to fix?
I don't know... everyone is so nice.
I don't know.I wonder.
Well, is there anything you'd like me to fix? Is there something you'd like me to fix?
Well, I'll ask the other side.
One word of love for all of you!
The Love
What is your ultimate goal as a talker?
I'm aiming for the Budokan now, but I want it to be a journey, not a goal,
My goal or dream is to stay with Tork-san as long as possible, even for one second,
I would like to do my best to stay there as long as I can.
Finally, a word of love to the members of Tohoku-san.
Yes, I know I'm always such a clumsy, no-good leader, but how can I help you in case of emergencies?
What do you do when there is an emergency? I am always such a clumsy, no-good leader, but when there is an emergency, they always ask me, "What are you going to do?
I really believe that the reason I am able to join Tohoku-san is because everyone always supports me.
Thank you for always being there for me.
Even when Karen was about to disappear, we all lined up to go together,
I really like the Tohoku-san members who always look at me when I am about to disappear,
Even when I walk down the street or look at the grass, it is only the members who turn it into fun,
I will do my best to be with you all from now on.
Thank you for everything.
100 Questions by Yoshin Tachibana has ended.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
Did you get to know him?
I would be happy if he likes me even though I am like this from now on,
I will live my life to the fullest.
So, this is Yoshin Tachibana.
Bye-bye.
Bye bye.